My O
name O
is O
Hicham B-PER
E-B I-PER
. O

I O
don't O
live O
in O
New-York B-LOC
. O

My O
name O
is O
Hicham B-PER
E-B I-PER
. O

I O
don't O
live O
in O
New-York B-LOC
. O
